fizzy.com 2001-06-13

# GreatDomains.com - The Internet's #1 Domain Name, Website, and Internet-based business brokerage service.

PRIVACY POLICY

This Policy was last revised on April 18, 2001.

**GreatDomains.com, Inc. (“GreatDomains.com”) is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. GreatDomains.com takes this commitment very seriously. We will not give, sell or otherwise share any of your personal information with any third party without your approval. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated.**

**How Your Information Is Gathered**

GreatDomains.com collects information in a variety of ways. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. When registering for GreatDomains.com’s services, the registration form requires you to give us contact information, such as your name, address, e-mail address,unique identifiers, and demographic information. In the course of using our site, we automatically track additional information, such as the URL that you just came from, which URL you go to next, and what browser you were using. Information of this sort is typically collected automatically by many sites. 

In addition, GreatDomains.com uses cookies for certain pages of our site. The use of cookies streamlines your use of and access to our Web site. Among other reasons, cookies allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session and enable us to provide information that is targeted to your interest. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your computer from our Web site and is stored on your computer’s hard drive. Many cookies are “session cookies” that are automatically deleted at the end of a session. You are always free to decline a cookie if your browser enables such a choice, however, in that case, your online session may be more cumbersome and may require you to reenter information that has already been entered.

If you choose to place an offer or to sell a Domain Name on our Web site, we will collect information about your purchasing and selling behavior. We may also collect comments provided by other users in our feedback area.

If you elect to use additional services provided by GreatDomains.com, such as our escrow services, additional financial and personal information will be collected, such as your billing address and other specific financial information, collected directly or from transaction documents used in the process to establish the financial resources necessary to conclude the transaction. Additional information may be obtained from many different sources, such as personal correspondence or e-mails that you send to us or that we may receive from third parties, other communications,or activities posted to our site.

Finally, please note that GreatDomains.com’s Web site is linked to other Web sites by way of hotlinks and advertisement banners. GreatDomains.com is not responsible for the content, or the privacy practices of such external Web sites. For these specific practices, you should refer to the specific privacy policy administered by each such Web site.

**How the Information Is Used**

GreatDomains.com uses personal information for internal purposes only, to provide those services that you are requesting, to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content and service offerings, to customize our site’s content and layout, and to further enhance the services that we provide. We may also use personally identifiable information about you to deliver information to you that, in some cases, is targeted to your interest, such as targeted banners and promotions.You can always remove yourself from receiving such information by notifying us by using the opt-out option in the “My Profile” page.

Mailing information, such as your e-mail address, may be used in rare situations for us to contact you regarding an administrative issue. Address and billing information may be used if you elect to use our escrow services, or in the event that we are entitled to a transfer fee for a sale conducted through our Web site.

We may also use information in the file that we maintain regarding your current and past activities in the unlikely event that we need to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems,or otherwise to enforce our User Agreement. At times, cross-sectional information may be used of multiple users to identify problems or resolve disputes.

In order to defer some of the costs of doing business, and thus, to be able to charge the user lower fees, GreatDomains.com generates additional revenue by way of delivering targeted advertisements. When delivering such advertisements, GreatDomains.com serves as the middleman, delivering the advertisement according to certain criteria requested by the advertisers, such as particular demographics. GreatDomains.com will then display the advertisement to users who meet that this criteria. In During this process, the third-party advertiser does not have access to your individual account information.

**With Whom Does GreatDomains.com Share Your Information?**

As a general rule, GreatDomains.com does not disclose any of your personally identifiable information, unless we have your specific permission, or under special circumstances, such as when we reasonably believe that the law requires that we do so. We do aggregate personally identifiable information and disclose such information in the aggregate as historical, statistical data for marketing, and promotional situations. However, in such situations, it is not possible to personally identify you or your personal information. Certain information, such as your password, credit card information, or bank account number would not be disclosed in such aggregate disclosures.

GreatDomains.com cooperates with all law enforcement inquiries and with third-parties who are enforcing their intellectual property or other proprietary rights. We, of course, also provide that the information which is necessary to facilitate the actual, ongoing commercial activities conducted on the GreatDomains.com Web site. For example, we will provide identifying information to the parties that have agreed upon the purchase and sale of a Domain Name, so that they may continue and conclude the transaction. All recipients of the transaction agree to the restrictions of on how they can use and disclose such information.

In sum, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not and cannot promise, and you cannot expect, that your personally identifiable communications will always remain private.

**Your Use of Other Users’ Information.**

As a seller, you will be sent certain private information identifying the buyer of your Internet Domain Name, and as a buyer, you will be sent identifying information of the seller. By entering into our User Agreement, you agree that any personally identifying information that you obtain through the GreatDomains.com Web site or through a GreatDomains.com-related communication or a GreatDomains.com-facilitated transaction, you are granted a limited license to use such information only for the furthering of the subject matter of the GreatDomains.com-related transaction, including GreatDomains.com-facilitated services, such as its escrow services. Upon conclusion of the transaction, you will remove and delete all copies in all forms of the personally-identifying third party information, other than one copy of only that data which is necessary for the archivaling of the transaction, unless you receive explicit, specific written approval from the Registrant of the personal information that you need not do so.

**Updating and Correcting Personally Identifying Information**

Once you register with GreatDomains.com, you will be able and are allowed to change your personally identifying information available at GreatDomains.com, including your e-mail address, user ID, name, address, telephone number, password, and credit card information. Upon your request, we will remove any of the above personally identifying information other than your name and user ID. We will send you a confirmation of the information that you requested us to remove and the date of its removal. We will retain in our files certain information in our files that you have requested us to remove for different purposes, such as to resolve potential dispute, troubleshoot problems,and otherwise enforce our User Agreement. Furthermore, certain circumstances could prevent the complete and permanent removal of such information from our databases such as technical constraints and the periodic backing up and archiving of our systems for disaster recovery purposes.

**General**

Our Privacy Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information that we collect. To the extent that you disclose information to other parties, even if you connected to those parties through the GreatDomains.com Web site, different rules may apply, and GreatDomains.com does not manage or control such information. GreatDomains.com implements industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal identifiable information, such as fire walls and SSL encryption. However, perfect security measures do not exist and we cannot guarantee that third parties cannot exercise sufficient resources to break down the protective systems that we have established and obtain your personal information.This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the GreatDomains.com User Agreement.

**Third Party Ad Serving**

GreatDomains.com uses a third party to serve the advertisements on our Web site and other Web sites. In the course of serving ads, these companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser, and may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to measure advertising effectiveness and provide advertisements to this and other sites about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, copy this link into a browser to view: _http://www.doubleclick.net/naiprivacy_

Our current provider and ad server is DoubleClick.
